RAYHAN PUTRA JAFANDI

089697907789 | rayhanputra100@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/rayhan-jafandi/ | https://my-portofolio-git-main-rayhanpjs-projects.vercel.app/

Gramaputri Tamansari Blok C12/34,

Hello, my name is Rayhan Putra Jafandi, i am a software developer focused on developing websites using PHP framework like Laravel, or Codeigniter Technology, Javascript framework like React JS or Next JS and Golang framework like Gin and Gorm. I have 2 years of experience as a web developer and have complited several website projects as well as doing maintenance and testing, familiar with frontend, backend and full-stack software development task. I am interest in learning new things and am looking for an opportunity to work in a company in a position that is relevant to the experience and skills i have. I am ready to work to achieve common goals

Work Experiences

PT Century Batteries Indonesia - Karawang Timur, Jawa Barat,

Mar 2023 - Apr 2024

Indonesia

Internship

- Take part in the development of digitalization projects through web application development using Codelgniter technology
- · Create innovative and responsive websites, ensuring optimal user experience
- Responsible for routine maintenance and updates to maintain site quality
- Create database design, implementation and maintenance using SQL Server to ensure data efficiency and reliabilityConduct comprehensive evaluations of each project, capturing opportunities for improvement and growth
- Provide constructive feedback to team members and relevant stakeholders
- · Collaborate with various departments to ensure deep understanding of business needs and implementation of customized solutions

Universitas Singaperbangsa Karawang - Karawang, Jawa

Jan 2022 - Jan 2024

Barat, Indonesia

Computer Lab Assistant

- Assisting lecturers in the process of implementing practicum
- Teaching practical courses
- Participate in the development of practical materials

CIMB Niaga - Remote Mar 2023

Web Editor

- Developed and implemented software solutions based on client requirements.
- Create new feature, refactor, maintenance and optimizing new/existing application.

Projects – (https://my-portofolio-git-main-rayhanpjs-projects.vercel.app/)

Car Zone - Final Project Sanbercode Golang - Next JS

- · Purpose: E-Commerce for buy a new or second car
- Technologies: Golang, Next JS, Shadon, Supabase, Postgre
- Features : Buying car, Monitoring buyer, Print Invoice, master data, edit profile

Dashboard Incomming - PT Century Batteries Indonesia

- · Purpose: Monitoring incomming suppliers at PT Century Batteries Indonesia
- Technologies: PHP, Codeigniter 4, Boostrap, SQL Server
- Features: Traffic chart monitoring for trucks in the area, Real-time supplier time records, Automatic data to server using cronjob, Download reports data today

Warehouse Management System – PT Century Batteries Indonesia

• Purpose: Dashboard for inputting items to dross, and for

- · inputting recycle material and waste
- Technologies: PHP, Codeigniter 4, Boostrap, SQL Server
- Features : Dross and recycle material input, Print dross weight and lead weight, Reports Dross and waste

E - WIP - PT Century Batteries Indonesia

- · Purpose: Monitoring incomming suppliers at PT Century Batteries Indonesia
- Technologies: PHP, Codeigniter 4, Boostrap, SQL Server
- Features: Traffic chart monitoring for trucks in the area, Real-time supplier time records, Automatic data to server using cronjob, Download reports data today

Cell Checking and Lithium Positioning - PT Century Batteries

Indonesia

- Purpose: Dashboard for inputting details of lithium batteries for positioning at cell
- Technologies: PHP, Codeigniter 4, Boostrap, SQL Server
- Features: Cell calculation, Detail input data for lithium batteries form QR, Cell checking Total data input for cells

Go Travel - Kampus Merdeka at Binar Academy (Fullstack Developer)

- · Purpose: Website for booking airline
- Technologies: Javascript, Node JS, React JS, Material UI, Postgre SQL
- Features: Login and register user, Edit user, Booking airline, Transaction History, Information of ticket, Wishlist Destination, Notification

Suratin Aja - Final Exam Project (Universitas Singaperbangsa Karawang)

- · Purpose: Manage request and auto generate campus latter like recommendation letter etc
- Technologies: PHP, Laravel 10, Boostrap, MYSQL
- Features: Login and register user, Edit user, Generate the selected letter, Approval or rejection request by Admin, List data request letter user

Toko Maju Aja Dulu – Final Exam Project Student Exchange Kampus Merdeka (Universitas Mulawarman)

- Purpose: Monitoring incomming suppliers at PT Century Batteries Indonesia
- Technologies: PHP, Codeigniter 4, Boostrap, SQL Server
- Features: Traffic chart monitoring for trucks in the area, Real-time supplier time records, Automatic data to server using cronjob, Download reports data today

Formal Education

Universitas Singaperbangsa Karawang - Jl. HS.Ronggo Waluyo, Puseurjaya,

Jun 2020 - Aug 2024

Telukjambe Timur, Karawang, Jawa Barat 41361

Fresh Graduation

SMK Negeri 1 Cikarang Barat - Jl. Raya Teuku Umar No.1, Gandasari, Kec.

Mar 2017 - Mar 2020

Cikarang Barat, Kabupaten Bekasi, Jawa Barat 17520

Informal Education

Sanbercode Foundation - Fullstack Developer

Jun 2024 - Aug 2024

Using Next JS and Golang

Get a scholarship from Sanbercode Foundation for the Full Stack Developer class using Next JS and Golang for 2 months intensively with real projects.

Binar Academy – Fullstack Developer

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022

Using React JS and Node JS

Study at Binar Academy Merdeka Campus Independent Study x Binar Academy Program Full Stack Website Developer Class using React JS and Node JS for 6 months intensively with real projects.

Organitation Experiences

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika - Karawang, Jawa Barat

Dec 2021 - Nov 2022

Head of Research and Development Departement

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika is a student organization at Singaperbangasa University, Karawang, Faculty of Informatics which will be a forum for students to learn new skill and experience.

- Responsible for running the work program of the Department
- Responsible to members of the Department
- Communicate and collaborate with other departments.

ADDITIONAL

- Technical: Python, SQL, PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Computer Network, Linux, Git, GitHub, GitLab, OOP, Microsoft Office.
- Languages: Fluent in Indonesian; Understand in English.